http://www.thermos.com/privacy

Product Technology
Search:
INTRODUCTION
Thermos L.L.C. (“Company” or “Thermos” respects your privacy and is committed to protecting it through our compliance with this policy (“Privacy Policy”) and any applicable laws or regulations.
This Privacy Policy, along with the Terms of Use form the agreement governing your use of www.Thermos.com (“Website”). As noted in the Terms of Use, Thermos has authorized a third party called Ally Commerce to run certain functions of the Website. In this Privacy Policy (as well as the Terms of Use), use the words “we” and “us” to refer to Thermos and Ally Commerce, collectively and individually, unless otherwise specified.
This Privacy Policy describes the personal information we collect about you, and how we use and share that information. This policy applies to personal information we collect when you register for this Website; subscribe to Thermos’ newsletter; enter one of our promotions (e.g., sweepstakes or contest), send us a question, access or use our Website, products, or services (collectively, the “Services”); or when you otherwise interact with us, including through phone, e-mail, text and other electronic messages. It does not apply to information collected by any third party, including through any application or content (including advertising) that may link to or be accessible from our Website or Services.
This Privacy Policy refers to personal information which is information that can be associated with a specific person and used to identify that person. Personal information does not include information that has been anonymized so that it does not identify a specific user, which may be used for any legal purpose.
This Privacy Policy covers the following topics:
Updates to the Privacy Policy
Sources of Information About You
Our Use of Information
Sharing of Information
Accessing, Updating, Transferring, or Removing Your Personal Information
Links to Other Web Sites
Children's Privacy
Your California Privacy Rights
Security
Contact Information
Effective Date
Please read this policy carefully to understand our policies and practices regarding your personal information and how we will treat it. If you do not agree with our policies and practices, your choice is not to use our Services. By accessing or using our Services, you agree to this Privacy Policy.
UPDATES TO THE PRIVACY POLICY
We may update, amend, revise or otherwise change this Privacy Policy from time to time. If we make changes, we endeavor to notify you by posting the updated policy and revising the “Effective Date” above. Your continued use of the Services constitutes your acceptance of the then-effective Privacy Policy. However, any changes will not apply to any disputes of which the parties have actual notice on or prior to the date the change is posted on either of the Websites.
SOURCES OF INFORMATION ABOUT YOU
We obtain information about you from a variety of sources, including you, your interaction with Thermos, Ally, our Website, and third parties. Such information may include your name, postal address, e-mail address, purchase history, reviews you post on our Website, date of birth, demographic information (such as age, gender, and language) telephone number, and credit card (if you make a purchase from the Website), among other personally identifiable information.
INFORMATION YOU PROVIDE TO US: If you use certain Services, you may be required to provide us certain information.
Information that you provide by filling in forms on our Website. This includes information provided at the time of registering to use our Services, subscribing to our Services, posting material, calling or emailing us, or requesting further information or services.
We may also ask you for information when you report a problem with our Services. Records and copies of your correspondence (including e-mail addresses), if you contact us. Your responses to surveys that we might ask you to complete for research purposes.
Details of transactions you carry out through our Services and of the fulfillment of your orders. Your search queries on our Website or through our Services.
INFORMATION WE COLLECT FROM YOUR USE OF THE SERVICES AND OTHER INTERACTIONS YOU HAVE WITH US:
We may collect your usage information about how you use the Services, including your access times, location, browser types and language, pages of our Website that you visit, how you interact with our emails, and Internet Protocol addresses. We may collect device-specific information when you access our Website or other Services, including your hardware model, operating system and version, unique device identifiers, mobile network information, and information about the device's interaction with our Services.
The information we collect automatically is statistical data and may or may not include personal information, but we may maintain it or associate it with personal information we collect in other ways or receive from third parties. It helps us to improve and to deliver better and more personalized Services, including by enabling us to:
Estimate our audience size and usage patterns.
Store information about your preferences, allowing us to customize our Services according to your individual interests.
Speed up your searches.
Recognize you when you return to our Services.
Send you emails inviting you to purchase items from our Website.
Serve relevant advertising content via email and other platforms.
The technologies we use for this automatic data collection may include:
Cookies (or browser cookies).A cookie is a small file placed on the hard drive of your computer. You may refuse to accept certain browser cookies by activating the appropriate setting on your browser.
Flash Cookies.Certain features of our Services may use local stored objects (or Flash cookies) to collect and store information about your preferences and navigation to, from and on our Services. Flash cookies are not managed by the same browser settings as are used for browser cookies.
Web Beacons.Pages of the Services or our e-mails may contain small electronic files known as web beacons (also referred to as clear gifs. pixel tags and single-pixel gifs) that permit us, for example, to count users who have visited those pages or opened an e-mail and for other related Website statistics (for example, recording the popularity of certain Website content and verifying system and server integrity).
The Website also may use third party service providers, such as Google Analytics or other similar services, to collect or exchange information about you or anonymized information. Google provides an explanation of how Google Analytics collects and uses information at the following link: https://policies.google.com/privacy/update?hl=en&gl=us. (This link is provided for your convenience, but the URL may change or become unavailable at any time.)
OUR USE OF INFORMATION
We use information about you to provide, maintain, personalize and improve our Services and to deliver the information and support your requests, including receipts, technical notices, security alerts, and support and administrative messages.
We may use information we collect to send you news and information about our Services and to communicate with you about products, services, contests, promotions, incentives, and rewards offered by us and select partners. You may opt out of receiving promotional emails or text messages from us by following the instructions in those emails or text messages. If you opt out, we may still send you non-promotional communications, such as messages about your account or our ongoing business relations.
We may also use information about you (i) to track and analyze trends and usage in connection with our Services; (ii) to process and deliver contest and promotion entries and rewards; (iii) to protect our rights or property; (iv) to compare information for accuracy; (v) to verify your identity; (vi) to investigate and prevent fraud or other illegal activities; and (vii) for any other purpose disclosed to you in connection with our Services.
Additionally, we use information that we collect about you or that you provide to us, including any personal information:
To provide you with information, products or services that you request from us.
To fulfill any other purpose for which you provide it.
To provide you with notices about your account/subscription, including expiration and renewal notices.
To carry out our obligations and enforce our rights arising from any contracts entered into between you and us, including for billing and collection.
To notify you about changes to our Services or any products or services we offer or provide though them.
In any other way we may describe when you provide the information.
For any other purpose with your consent.
We may use the information we have collected from you to enable us to display advertisements.
We may use third-party service providers to process and store personal information in the United States and other countries.
We also may use your personal information for additional purposes as expressly described in the Official Rules posted for each promotion (e.g., contest or sweepstakes).
SHARING OF INFORMATION
We may share personal information about you as follows:
To our subsidiaries and affiliates.
To contractors, service providers and other third parties we use to support our business and who are bound by contractual obligations to keep personal information confidential and use it only for the purposes for which we disclose it to them.
To comply with any court order, law or legal process, including to respond to any government or regulatory request.
To enforce or apply our Terms of Use , and other agreements, including for billing and collection purposes.
If we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to protect the rights, property, or safety of Thermos, Ally, our customers or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.
To fulfill the purpose for which you provide it.
With third parties that help us run advertising campaigns, contests, special offers, or other events or activities in connection with our Services.
For any lawful purpose, including, without limitation, selling your data to third parties parties (unless you are a California resident who has requested not to have your information sold or such sale is otherwise not permitted by law)
With your consent or direction.
We may also share non-personally identifiable information (aggregated or otherwise) with third parties for any reason.
ACCESSING, UPDATING, TRANSFERRING OR REMOVING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION
You may request to update, change, or delete your personal information, object to the processing of your personal information, withdraw your consent the processing of your personal information, request that we do not sell your personal information to third parties, or request a copy of your personal information that we hold, disclosed, or sold by contacting us at [email protected] or mailing us at: Thermos L.L.C., Attn: General Counsel, 475 N. Martingale Road, Suite 1100, Schaumburg IL 60173. Also, if you created an account on Thermos.com, then you may manage certain of your user information by accessing your “My Account” page. You can also ask us how we use your personal information, the source of your personal information, to update or amend your personal information if you believe it is inaccurate, remove your personal information from our records entirely, send copies of your personal information to you or a third party in a commonly used format, to request that we do not subject you or your personal information to automated decision-making, or otherwise restrict our use of your personal information by emailing us at [email protected], calling us at 847.439.7821, or by accessing your “My Account” page.
Before we provide a substantive response to your request, we may ask you for certain identifying information to confirm your identity and your right to access the personal information that we hold about you or that you are authorized to access this information if you are an agent. In certain circumstances, we reserve the right to charge a reasonable fee to comply with your request to change, transfer, or provide details about your personal information. We may, at our option, maintain your personal information until you withdraw your consent, or ask us to delete or transfer the information, to the extent otherwise permitted by law.
Rights of California Residents
Some data protection laws, such as the California Consumer Privacy Act (CCPA) and California Civil Code Section § 1798.83, provide California residents with certain rights in connection with personal information you have shared with us. If you are a California resident, you may have the following rights and we respect those rights:
The right to know what personal information is collected, used, shared or sold, both as to the categories and specific pieces of personal information in the previous 12 months; We endeavor to respond to verified requests within 45 days, with a 45 day extension if we provide a notice within the first 45 day period (as applicable under the CCPA). California consumers may make up to two personal information requests in a 12 month period; Certain requests under California Civil Code Section § 1798.83 are specific to uses of personal information for direct marketing purposes;
The right to delete personal information held by businesses and by extension, a business’s service provider;
The right to opt-out of sale of personal information. Consumers are able to direct a business that sells personal information to stop selling that information. Children under the age of 16 must provide opt in consent, with a parent or guardian consenting for children under 13.
The right to non-discrimination in terms of price or service when a consumer exercises a privacy right under CCPA.
LINKS TO OTHER WEB SITES: THIRD PARTY APPLICATIONS
Thermos is not responsible for any practices employed by websites linked to or from our Website, nor their information or content. Please remember that when you use a link to go from our Website to another website, this Privacy Policy is no longer in effect. Your browsing and interaction on any other Website is subject to that Website’s own rules and policies. Please read over those rules and policies before proceeding. Additionally, some content or applications, including advertisements, on or through the Services are served by third-parties, including advertisers, ad networks and servers, content providers and application providers. These third parties may use cookies, alone or in conjunction with web beacons or other tracking technologies, to collect information about you when you use our Services. The information they collect may be associated with your personal information or they may collect information, including personal information, about your online activities over time and across different websites and other online services. They may use this information to provide you with interest-based (behavioral) advertising or other targeted content. We do not control these third parties' tracking technologies or how they may be used. If you have any questions about an advertisement or other targeted content, you should contact the responsible provider directly.
CHILDREN'S POLICY
The Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act was created to protect children under the age of 13 from unsuspecting acts or practices in conjunction with collecting, using, and disclosing any information about them. Our Services are not intended for anyone under the age of 13. If you are under 13, do not use or provide any information on the Website or through our Services. In addition, users under 18 years of age are not allowed to make purchases. If we learn we have collected or received personal information from a child under 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information. If you are a parent or guardian or otherwise believe we might have any information from or about a child under 13, please contact us so that we can delete the child's information. The Services will never knowingly accept, collect, maintain or use any information from a child under the age of 13. If a child whom we know to be under the age of 13 sends personal information to us online, we will only use that information to respond directly to that child or notify parents. Where appropriate, we may ask you to indicate your age to verify compliance with these policies.
CALIFORNIA AND DELAWARE "DO NOT TRACK' DISCLOSURES
California and Delaware law require us to indicate whether we honor “Do Not Track” settings in your browser concerning targeted advertising. “Do Not Track” is a standard that is currently under development. As it is not yet finalized, we adhere to the standards set out in this Privacy Policy and do not monitor or follow any Do Not Track browser requests.
SECURITY
The safety and security of your personal information also depends on you. Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password for access to certain parts of our Services, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share your password with anyone. Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we do take many precautions to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of your personal information transmitted to or through our Services. Any transmission of personal information is at your own risk. We are not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on or within the Services.
CONTACT INFORMATION
Please contact us with any questions or concerns regarding our policy at this address: [email protected]
Thermos L.L.C. Attention: General Counsel 475 N. Martingale Road Suite 1100Schaumburg IL 60173
Get the best from thermos
There are some errors in your form.
Invalid Email Address.
Submit
Thank You
For more details, please refer to our Privacy Policy. By clicking 'Submit' you consent to receive Thermos L.L.C. marketing and promotional emails. You can unsubscribe at any time.
Online order assistance
844-431-1995
Call hours
MON-FRI 8AM - 6PM ET excluding holidays
Customer service
1-800-831-9242
Send Us A Message
Worldwide Offices
Do Not Sell My Info
©2018-2020 Thermos L.L.C. All Right Reserved. THERMOS is a registered trademark in over 115 countries. E-commerce functions provided by Ally Commerce, authorized by Thermos L.L.C.
